Preliminary Guide to the Joe Szabo Papers and Collection of Original Comic Art, 1960s-2000s SPEC.CGA.JGS
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Effat, Esmail, 1990-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 84)
- Eggstein, Jo, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 89)
- Ehrenburg, Boris, 1989 (Box JGS 4, Folder 90)
- Eisman, Hy, 1987-1995 (Box JGS 4, Folder 91)
- Eisner, Will, 1988-1994 (Box JGS 4, Folder 92)
- El-Zawawy, circa 1973 (Box JGS 4, Folder 93)
- Ella, El Y Pancu, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 94)
- Elvestuen, Per, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 95)
- Emerson, Ken, 1987-1989 (Box JGS 4, Folder 96)
- Emmerson, Rod, 1990 (Box JGS 4, Folder 97)
- Emser, James, 1990 (Box JGS 4, Folder 98)
- Emu, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 4, Folder 99)
- Englehart, Bob, 1983-1990 (Box JGS 4, Folder 100)
- Erdogan, Basol, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 101)
- Erkanli, Ahmet, 1994-1997 (Box JGS 4, Folder 102)
- Erlich, Gustav, 1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 103)
- Ernst, Serge, 1991 (Box JGS 4, Folder 104)
- Ernst, Tim, 1989-1997 (Box JGS 4, Folder 105, Box JGS 15, Folder 58)
- Eschenbach, Christopher, 2001 (Box JGS 4, Folder 106)
- Esmail, M. Effat Abd el-Azim, 1984-2001 (Box JGS 4, Folder 107-108)
- Esquivel, Arcadio, 1985-1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 109)
- Etzensperger, T., 1991 (Box JGS 4, Folder 110)
- Evans, Greg, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 111)
- Evers, Frank, 1986 (Box JGS 4, Folder 112)
- Fabry, Janos, 1990 (Box JGS 4, Folder 113)
- Facta, Bernardo, 1988-1999 (Box JGS 4, Folder 114, Box JGS 15, Folder 59)
- Fahr, 1994-1997 (Box JGS 4, Folder 115)
- Fagan, Kevin, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 116)
- Fai, Chow Ming, 1991 (Box JGS 4, Folder 117)
- Falardeau, Mira, 1986-1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 118)
- Fan, Qiang, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 119)
- Farahani, Hadi, 1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 120)
- Fareed, 1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 121)
- Faria, Jeff, 1987-1992 (Box JGS 4, Folder 122)
- Farhat, Gomaa, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 123)
- Farksas, Ya'Acov, 1994 (Box JGS 4, Folder 124)
- Farris, Joseph, circa 1989 (Box JGS 5, Folder 1)
- Faur, Jean-Claude, 1986-1994 (Box JGS 15, Folder 60)
- Fazlic, Hasan, 1988 (Box JGS 5, Folder 2)
- Fearing, Jerry, 1989-1990 (Box JGS 5, Folder 3)
- Feggo, Felipe, 1993 (Box JGS 5, Folder 5)
- Fei, Xu Peng, 1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 6)
- Feiffer, Jules, 1987-1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 7)
- Feign, Larry, 1986-1997 (Box JGS 5, Folder 8)
- Felix, 1987-1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 9)
- Fera, Dragos, 1991 (Box JGS 5, Folder 10)
- Ferretti, James, 1991 (Box JGS 5, Folder 11)
- Ferrom, EQ, circa 1983 (Box JGS 5, Folder 12)
- Fiddy, Roland, 1984-1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 13)
- Fiezabadi, M., 1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 14)
- Figueras, Alfons, 1987 (Box JGS 5, Folder 15)
- Fikov, Fiko, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 16)
- Filho, Deodato, 1983-1986 (Box JGS 5, Folder 17)
- Filipova, Nejna, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 18)
- Firzlaff, Hans, 1987-1989 (Box JGS 5, Folder 19)
- Fischetti, John, 1976 (Box JGS 5, Folder 20)
- Fisher, Elizabeth, 1994 (Box JGS 5, Folder 21)
- Fisher, Eric, 1989-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 61)
- Fisher, Philip, 1975 (Box JGS 5, Folder 22)
- Fisher, Yu Tu, 1983-1985 (Box JGS 5, Folder 23)
- Fitzgerald, T., 1990 (Box JGS 5, Folder 24)
- Flores, Philip A., 1991-1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 25)
- Flores, Roger Sanchez, 1988-1997 (Box JGS 5, Folder 26)
- Flynt, Debbie, 1995-1996 (Box JGS 5, Folder 27)
- Foldvari, Kornell, 1996-1998 (Box JGS 15, Folder 62)
- Fontanarrosa, 1991 (Box JGS 5, Folder 28)
- Foote, Dan, 1992-1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 29)
- Forney, Jerry, 1994 (Box JGS 5, Folder 30)
- Foster, Walter, 1990 (Box JGS 21, Folder 56)
- Fox, Fontaine, 1954 (Box JGS 5, Folder 31)
- Fox, Gill, 1978-1989 (Box JGS 5, Folder 32)
- Foyle, Linsay, 1993-1994 (Box JGS 5, Folder 33)
- Fradon, Ramona, 1990 (Box JGS 5, Folder 34)
- Franchioni, A., 1984-1988 (Box JGS 5, Folder 35)
- Francois, Andre, 1993 (Box JGS 5, Folder 36)
- Frank, Phil, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 37)
- Freleng, Friz, 1990-1993 (Box JGS 5, Folder 38)
- Friedmann, Alex, 2000 (Box JGS 5, Folder 39)
- Friers, Rowel, 1990 (Box JGS 5, Folder 40)
- Frohn, Axel, 1986-1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 41)
- Fry, Michael, 1990-1997 (Box JGS 5, Folder 42)
- Frye, Eldon, 1970-1991 (Box JGS 5, Folder 43)
- Fuchs, Cesar, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 44)
- Fuchsel, Franz, 1986-1991 (Box JGS 5, Folder 45)
- Fujii, Mitchell, 1986 (Box JGS 5, Folder 46)
- Furrer, Jurg, 1986 (Box JGS 5, Folder 47)
- Furtounov, Stefan, 1988-1989 (Box JGS 5, Folder 48)
- Fuyang, Wang, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 49)
- Gaczol, Robert, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 50)
- Gagla, Faruk, 1993 (Box JGS 5, Folder 51)
- Gakin, Lutfu, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 52)
- Galabov, Iliya, 1986-1988 (Box JGS 5, Folder 53)
- Galindo, Felipe, 1990-1996 (Box JGS 5, Folder 54)
- Galis, Cengiz, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 55)
- Galvao, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 56)
- Gamble, 1986-1987 (Box JGS 5, Folder 57)
- Gantt, Barry, 1989-1997 (Box JGS 5, Folder 58)
- Ganz, Bob, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 59)
- Gao, Ge, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 60)
- Garabet, Fares, 1990-1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 61)
- Garcia, Dave, 1983-1989 (Box JGS 5, Folder 62)
- Gardosh, Kariel, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 63)
- Garrincha, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 64)
- Garrity, Martin E., 1989 (Box JGS 5, Folder 65)
- Garzon, 1990 (Box JGS 5, Folder 66)
- Gaspirtz, Oliver, 1994 (Box JGS 5, Folder 67)
- Gataullin, Rooshan (Box JGS 5, Folder 68)
- Gately, George, 1989 (Box JGS 5, Folder 69)
- Gautier, Dick, 1991 (Box JGS 5, Folder 70)
- Gautier, G., undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 71)
- Gavco, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 72)
- Gazdov, Ivan, 1990-1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 73)
- Geary, Rick, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 74)
- Gekke, circa 1987 (Box JGS 5, Folder 75)
- Gen-Hua, Zhu, 1989-1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 76)
- Georgiev, Borislav, 1992-1997 (Box JGS 5, Folder 77)
- Gerald, 1989-1996 (Box JGS 5, Folder 78)
- Gerberg, Mort, 1976 (Box JGS 5, Folder 79)
- Gerstein, Mel, 1988-1997 (Box JGS 5, Folder 80)
- Geszti, Gabor, 1988-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 63, Box JGS 5, Folder 81)
- Geza, Dr. Halasz, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 82)
- Gialanella, L., undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 83)
- Gibbons, Vic, 1987 (Box JGS 5, Folder 84)
- Gibbs, Maureen, 1990 (Box JGS 5, Folder 85)
- Gilchrist, B., 1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 86)
- Giles, circa 1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 87)
- Gilev, Anatolij, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 5, Folder 88)
- Gilfeather, Martha, 1991 (Box JGS 5, Folder 89)
- Gillett, Mike, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 90)
- Gintchev, Ivan, 1988-1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 64, Box JGS 5, Folder 91)
- Gitt, Vladimir, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 92)
- Glasbergen, Randy, 1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 93)
- Glusal, Randy, 1988 (Box JGS 5, Folder 94)
- Goderis, Ludo, 1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 95)
- Goebel, Robert, 1990 (Box JGS 5, Folder 96)
- Goetz, Kurt, 1992-1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 97)
- Goker, circa 1969 (Box JGS 5, Folder 98)
- Goldberg, Rube, 1996 (Box JGS 5, Folder 99)
- Golding, Matt, 1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 100)
- Goldman, Stuart, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 101)
- Golovich, Stan, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 102)
- Gomez, Pepe, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 103)
- Gondot, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 104)
- Gonick, Larry, 1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 105)
- Gonzales, E., 1993-1994 (Box JGS 5, Folder 106)
- Goodwin, William, 1991 (Box JGS 5, Folder 107)
- Gorbiev, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 108)
- Gorny, Eugeniusz, 1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 109)
- Gould, Chester, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 110)
- Gould, Steve, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 111)
- Gourgiotis, Spyros, 1993 (Box JGS 5, Folder 112)
- Graabak, Carsten, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 113)
- Grace, Bud, 1990-1996 (Box JGS 5, Folder 114)
- Graff, Finn, 1990-1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 115)
- Graham, Bill, circa 1994 (Box JGS 5, Folder 116)
- Gravett, Paul, 1993-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 65)
- Grbin, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 117)
- Green, Adam, 1993 (Box JGS 5, Folder 118)
- Greenberg, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 5, Folder 119)
- Greenblatt, M., 1994 (Box JGS 5, Folder 120)
- Griffer, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 5, Folder 121)
- Griffin, circa 1991 (Box JGS 5, Folder 122)
- Griffith, Bill, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 123)
- Grigo, Ernest, 1997 (Box JGS 5, Folder 124)
- Grimes, Mary Ann, 1997 (Box JGS 5, Folder 125)
- Gringle, Paul, 1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 126)
- Groening, Matt, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 5, Folder 127)
- Grogan, Tony, 1990-1994 (Box JGS 5, Folder 128, Box JGS 15, Folder 66)
- Groot, Klaas, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 129)
- Gross, S., undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 130)
- Grossman, Andy, 1989 (Box JGS 5, Folder 131)
- Grosso, Jorge, 1986 (Box JGS 5, Folder 132)
- Grosu, Konstantin, 1996 (Box JGS 5, Folder 133)
- Grozev, Mitco, 1993 (Box JGS 5, Folder 134)
- Grupe, Fritz H., 1995 (Box JGS 5, Folder 135)
- Guangjun, Li, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 136)
- Guillen, Richard P., undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 137)
- Guisewite, Cathy, 1990-1994 (Box JGS 5, Folder 138)
- Gujjarappa, B.G., 1990-1992 (Box JGS 5, Folder 139)
- Guren, Peter, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 5, Folder 140)
- Gutierrez, 1993 (Box JGS 5, Folder 141)
- Guzina, Ranko, undated (Box JGS 5, Folder 142)
- Gvozdanovic, R., 1985-1986 (Box JGS 5, Folder 143)
- Haag, Greg, 1989-1994 (Box JGS 15, Folder 1, Folder 67)
- Habib, Ahsan, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 2)
- Hachfield, Rainer, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 3)
- Haddad, Habib, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 4)
- Hadi, Purmama, 1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 5)
- Hadjigregoriou, Demitrakis, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 6)
- Hadvigova, Zuzana, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 7)
- Haem, Hans, 1966-2002 (Box JGS 14, Folder 8)
- Hafezi, Nader, 1994 (Box JGS 15, Folder 9)
- Haitzinger, Horst, circa 1994 (Box JGS 15, Folder 10)
- Hajagha, Gholamhosseein, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 11)
- Hajnos, Miroslav, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 12)
- Hakansson, Lars-Erik, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 13)
- Hakem, Hassan, 1997 (Box JGS 15, Folder 14)
- Halas, John, 1989-1990 (Box JGS 15, Folder 15)
- Hall, Doug, circa 1988 (Box JGS 15, Folder 16)
- Hall, Oliver A., 1993-1994 (Box JGS 15, Folder 17)
- Hamad, Nabil Abou, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 15, Folder 18)
- Hamel, Jean Yues, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 19)
- Hamlin, V.T., undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 20)
- Hamm, Jack, 1943-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 21)
- Hancock, Malcolm (Mal), 1981 (Box JGS 15, Folder 22)
- Hande, Jack, 1993-1994 (Box JGS 15, Folder 23)
- Handlesman, Walt, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 24)
- Handzon, Vanda, 1989-1992 (Box JGS 15, Folder 25)
- Hanel, Walter, 1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 26)
- Hapka, Josef, 1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 27)
- Haramija, Ivan, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 15, Folder 29)
- Harca, circa 1995 (Box JGS 15, Folder 30)
- Hargreaues, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 31)
- Harling, Laura, 1995 (Box JGS 15, Folder 32)
- Harrington, Oliver, 1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 33)
- Harrington, Patrick, 1992-1997 (Box JGS 15, Folder 34)
- Harris, Ernest A., 1989 (Box JGS 15, Folder 35)
- Hart, John, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 36)
- Harte, Mary Ellen, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 37)
- Harun, Harunoor, 1988-1994 (Box JGS 15, Folder 68)
- Harvey, Milton, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 38)
- Haryadi, A.L., circa 1987 (Box JGS 15, Folder 39)
- Hassan, Hakim, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 40)
- Hatcher, Don, 1990 (Box JGS 15, Folder 41)
- Hatchfield, Rainer, 1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 42)
- Hatnean, C., undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 43)
- Hayduk, V., 1990 (Box JGS 15, Folder 44)
- Hazelton, Gene, 1975 (Box JGS 15, Folder 45)
- Heimann, Rolf, 1984-1998 (Box JGS 15, Folder 46, Folder 69)
- Heimdahl, Ralph, 1976 (Box JGS 15, Folder 47)
- Heino, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 48)
- Heins, Michael, 1992 (Box JGS 15, Folder 49)
- Helioflores, undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 50)
- Heller, Robin, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 15, Folder 51)
- Henniger, Barbara, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 52)
- Henson, John V., undated (Box JGS 15, Folder 53)
- Heritage, W.E., 1994 (Box JGS 6, Folder 1)
- Herman, Vic, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 2)
- Hermann, Poppe (Popps), undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 3)
- Hernandez, Jose, 1988-1994 (Box JGS 6, Folder 4)
- Herodes, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 5)
- Herrera, Diego (Yayo), 1984-1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 6)
- Herrera, Jose Arles, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 7)
- Herriman, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 8)
- Huxley, Quentin, circa 1986 (Box JGS 6, Folder 9)
- Higgins, Tom, 1987-1992 (Box JGS 6, Folder 10)
- Hihatov, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 11)
- Hill, Draper, 1988 (Box JGS 6, Folder 12)
- Hinchberger, Bill, 1989 (Box JGS 6, Folder 13)
- Hinze, Heinrich, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 14)
- Hirose Toru, 1989 (Box JGS 6, Folder 15)
- Hirschfeld, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 16)
- Hivatas, Nehez, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 17)
- Hjorth-Jorgensen, Anders, 1994-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 70)
- Hodgins, Dick, 1988 (Box JGS 6, Folder 18)
- Hoest, Bill, 1985-1988 (Box JGS 6, Folder 19)
- Hoffman, Frank, 1987-1994 (Box JGS 6, Folder 20)
- Hoffmann, Nancy, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 21)
- Hogan, Bill, 1989-1994 (Box JGS 6, Folder 22)
- Hogan, Mike, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 23)
- Hogarth, Burne, 1977 (Box JGS 15, Folder 54)
- Holbrook, Bill, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 15, Folder 55)
- Hollenstein, Walti, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 56)
- Holman, Bill, 1977 (Box JGS 6, Folder 24)
- Holmes, Frank, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 25)
- Holz, Eberhard, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 26)
- Hook, Geoff, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 27)
- Horn, Maurice, 1986-1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 71)
- Hosabettu, Vasantha, 1994-1996 (Box JGS 6, Folder 28)
- Hovivian, Rene, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 29)
- Hruby, Jan, 1986 (Box JGS 6, Folder 30)
- Hryhoriev, Yevhen, 1988 (Box JGS 6, Folder 31)
- Huber, Oswald, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 32)
- Huck, Gary, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 33)
- Hudkins, Arkie, 1991 (Box JGS 6, Folder 34)
- Huffaker, Sandy, 1991 (Box JGS 6, Folder 35)
- Hugg, Martin, 1989 (Box JGS 6, Folder 36)
- Hublikar, G.Y., undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 37)
- Hulme, Etta, 1989 (Box JGS 6, Folder 38)
- Hummel, Jim, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 6, Folder 39)
- Hunt, Dale, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 40)
- Hurd, Jud, 1986-1989 (Box JGS 6, Folder 41)
- Hurmatovich, G.M., undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 42)
- Hurt, 1990 (Box JGS 6, Folder 43)
- Hussain, Irfan, 1987 (Box JGS 6, Folder 44)
- Ignat, Mihai, 1994 (Box JGS 6, Folder 45)
- Imahase, Harum, 1995 (Box JGS 6, Folder 46)
- Indus, Christian, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 47)
- Ioan, H.G., undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 48)
- Ioneseu, 1994 (Box JGS 6, Folder 49)
- Ionita, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 50)
- Iracheta, Sergio, 1995 (Box JGS 6, Folder 51)
- Isaac, Norman, 1988-2005 (Box JGS 15, Folder 84, Box JGS 6, Folder 52)
- Islam, Nazrul, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 53)
- Ivantchev, Ivaylo, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 54)
- Jacob, Stephen, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 55)
- Jacquemin, Dominique, 1988-1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 56)
- Jaffee, Al, 1992 (Box JGS 6, Folder 57)
- Jago, Mic, 1988-1996 (Box JGS 6, Folder 58, Box JGS 15, Folder 72)
- Jagodic, Stane, circa 1995 (Box JGS 6, Folder 59)
- Jahsnowski, S., 1991 (Box JGS 6, Folder 60)
- Jakir, Hossain, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 61)
- James, Vezell, 1992-1994 (Box JGS 6, Folder 62)
- Jamiol, P.T., 1993-1994 (Box JGS 6, Folder 63)
- Jankovic, A., undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 64)
- Jankowski, A., 1986-1988 (Box JGS 6, Folder 65)
- Janocua, Blu, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 66)
- Janos, Hermann, 2003 (Box JGS 6, Folder 67)
- Janos, Nagy, 1988 (Box JGS 6, Folder 68)
- Janssen, Tom, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 69)
- Jantze, Michael, 1990 (Box JGS 6, Folder 70)
- Januszewski, Z., 1975-1992 (Box JGS 6, Folder 71)
- Jarape, 1985-1990 (Box JGS 6, Folder 72)
- Javadi, Mahmoud, 1992 (Box JGS 6, Folder 73)
- Jefferies, F., 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 74)
- Jessica, John, 1994 (Box JGS 6, Folder 75)
- Jian-Hua, By Li, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 76)
- Jian-Ming, Wang, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 77)
- Jingquan, Zou, 1991 (Box JGS 6, Folder 78)
- Johnson, J., 1996-1997 (Box JGS 6, Folder 79)
- Johnson, K., 1996 (Box JGS 6, Folder 80)
- Johnston, Lynn, 1988-1989 (Box JGS 6, Folder 81)
- Joko, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 82)
- Jonaitis, Alvydas, 1986-1991 (Box JGS 6, Folder 83)
- Jones, Chuck, 2002 (Box JGS 6, Folder 84)
- Jones, Randy, 1988-1995 (Box JGS 6, Folder 85)
- Jones, Yardley, 1995 (Box JGS 6, Folder 86)
- Jonik, John, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 6, Folder 87)
- Joole, C., 1992 (Box JGS 6, Folder 88)
- Jovanovic, Zoran, 1983-1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 89)
- Juchtmans, D., 1993-1996 (Box JGS 6, Folder 90)
- Juhas, Libomir, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 91)
- Jujka, Zbigniew, 1980-1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 92)
- Jung, J., 1995 (Box JGS 6, Folder 93)
- Jus, 1982 (Box JGS 6, Folder 94)
- Kabachev, Vladimir, 1987-1998 (Box JGS 6, Folder 95)
- Kabak, Mehmet, 1986 (Box JGS 6, Folder 96)
- Ka-Batembo, Katti, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 97)
- Kabi, Ahmad, 1990 (Box JGS 6, Folder 98)
- Kadam, D.K., 1991-1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 99)
- Kalantarzadeh, Koorosh, circa 1994 (Box JGS 6, Folder 100)
- Kalemei, Mustafa, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 101)
- Kallaugher, Kevin, 1990-1995 (Box JGS 6, Folder 102)
- Kambiz, undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 103)
- Kamel, Adel, 1991 (Box JGS 6, Folder 104)
- Kapusta, Janusz, circa 1988 (Box JGS 6, Folder 105)
- Kapusta, Nickolai, 1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 106)
- Karimzadeh, Hassan, 1994-1996 (Box JGS 6, Folder 107)
- Karistiani, I., 1989-1996 (Box JGS 6, Folder 108, Box JGS 15, Folder 73)
- Karlson, Gustav, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 6, Folder 109)
- Kasesalu, A., 1982 (Album JGS 6, Folder 110)
- Kashankov, V., undated (Box JGS 6, Folder 111)
- Kaste, Peter, 1985-1995 (Box JGS 6, Folder 112)
- Katz, Shemuel A., 1990-1994 (Box JGS 6, Folder 113)
- Kauffmann, Jochen (Joka), 1991 (Box JGS 6, Folder 114)
- Kaufman, Charles, 1990 (Box JGS 6, Folder 115)
- Kaupert, 1990 (Box JGS 6, Folder 116)
- Kayra, Musa, 1987-1991 (Box JGS 6, Folder 117)
- Kazanevskiy, Vladimir, 1988-2002 (Box JGS 6, Folder 118-119, Box JGS 7, Folder 1, Box JGS 15, Folder 74)
- Kazanskij, A., undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 2)
- Keane, Bil, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 7, Folder 3)
- Keefe, Mike, 1991 (Album JGS 7, Folder 4)
- Keegan, Ken, 1989 (Box JGS 7, Folder 5)
- Keiss, Ed, 1978-1990 (Box JGS 7, Folder 6)
- Kell, Gary, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 7, Folder 7)
- Kemchs, Arturo, 1989-1997 (Box JGS 7, Folder 8, Box JGS 15, Folder 75)
- Kemsley, James, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 9)
- Kerem, Juri, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 10)
- Ketcham, Henry, 1975 (Box JGS 7, Folder 11)
- Keusch, Bruno, 1986-1991 (Box JGS 7, Folder 12)
- Key, Ted, 1987-1989 (Box JGS 7, Folder 13)
- Keyes, Graeme, circa 1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 14)
- Khasabov, Sergey, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 15)
- Khosrowshad, K., 1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 16)
- Kirby, Jack, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 17)
- Kirby, L.J., 2008 (Box JGS 7, Folder 18)
- Kiriakov, Dimitar, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 19)
- Kirilov, 1991 (Box JGS 7, Folder 20)
- Kirkland, J.E., circa 1986 (Box JGS 7, Folder 21)
- Kirschen, 1990 (Box JGS 7, Folder 22)
- Klaic, Vjekoslav, 1989-1990 (Box JGS 7, Folder 23)
- Klas, Aleksandar, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 24)
- Klein, David, 1988 (Box JGS 7, Folder 25)
- Klubok, Jess, 1994 (Box JGS 7, Folder 26)
- Klucik, Peter, 1988-1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 27)
- Kluskowski, Darryl, circa 1992 (Box JGS 7, Folder 28)
- Kniecicki, P., undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 29)
- Knokke-Heist, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 30)
- Kobylinski, Szymon, 1991 (Box JGS 7, Folder 31)
- Kocagoz, Canol, 1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 32)
- Kocak, Asraf, 1982-1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 33)
- Koch, Arno, 1982-1987 (Box JGS 7, Folder 34)
- Koestana, J., 1989-1996 (Box JGS 7, Folder 35)
- Kohlsaat, Peter, 1989-1990 (Box JGS 7, Folder 36)
- Kolarov, Vladimir, 1989-1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 37)
- Kolkman, Richard, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 38)
- Kolsti, Paul, 1989-1994 (Box JGS 7, Folder 39)
- Komarnitski, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 40)
- Komo, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 41)
- Kononov, Dmitry, circa 1991 (Box JGS 7, Folder 42)
- Konyakhin, Sergei, 1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 43)
- Koopersmith, Adrienne Sioux, 1992-1994 (Box JGS 7, Folder 44-45)
- Koorosh, Kalantarzadeh, 1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 55)
- Kopelnitskiy, Igor, 1990 (Box JGS 7, Folder 46)
- Koraksic, Predrag (Corax), 1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 47)
- Koren, Ed, 1991 (Box JGS 7, Folder 48)
- Korimi, Karim, 1997 (Box JGS 7, Folder 49)
- Korolev, Dmitriy, 1991 (Box JGS 7, Folder 50)
- Kosanovic, Milenko, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 51)
- Kosobukin, Jurij, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 52)
- Koshonski, Tom, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 53)
- Kostov, P.D., 1990-1991 (Box JGS 7, Folder 54)
- Kostovetsky, G., undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 56)
- Kostovicik, Dusan, 1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 57)
- Kotbas, Muammer, 1991 (Box JGS 7, Folder 58)
- Kotreba, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 7, Folder 59)
- Kotrha, L., 1981-1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 60)
- Kourosh, Solaimani, circa 1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 63)
- Kovacik, Ivan, circa 1994 (Box JGS 7, Folder 61)
- Kovalenko, Vladimir, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 62)
- Kovarik, Bretislav, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 64)
- Kozlowski, M., 1988-1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 65)
- Kozyra, Tomas, 1990 (Box JGS 7, Folder 66)
- Krahn, Fenando, 1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 67)
- Kreffel, M., 1988-1989 (Box JGS 7, Folder 68)
- Krenner, Istvan, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 69)
- Krieger, Bob, 1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 70)
- Krippl, Gustav, 1992-1998 (Box JGS 7, Folder 71)
- Kripto, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 72)
- Kristian, circa 1996 (Box JGS 7, Folder 73)
- Krmasek, Milos, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 74)
- Krolikowski, Aaron, circa 1992 (Box JGS 7, Folder 75)
- Krstesky, Goran, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 76)
- Kruger, Sebastian, 1992 (Box JGS 7, Folder 77)
- Ku, Daniel, 1989-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 76)
- Kubert, Joe, 1988-1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 78)
- Kudranski, Mariusz, 1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 79)
- Kulkarni, Abhimanyu, 1986 (Box JGS 7, Folder 80)
- Kulinich, P., 1989-1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 81-82)
- Kumermann, 1988-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 77)
- Kuncoro, T.W., undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 83)
- Kunin, Gerardo, 1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 84)
- Kuper, Peter, 1988-1993 (Box JGS 7, Folder 85)
- Kupferberg, Tuli, undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 86)
- Kurtev, K., 1988-1990 (Box JGS 7, Folder 87)
- Kurtu, Valeri, 1990-1995 (Box JGS 7, Folder 88)
- Kurtz, H., undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 89)
- Kutal, Firuz, 1984-1988 (Box JGS 7, Folder 90)
- Kutca, Serdar, circa 1986 (Box JGS 7, Folder 91)
- Kverneland, S., undated (Box JGS 7, Folder 92)
- LaCroix, Mario, 1994 (Box JGS 8, Folder 1)
- LaFontaine, Ben, 1990-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 2)
- LaFontaine, Rob, 1994 (Box JGS 8, Folder 3)
- Laikin, Aron, 1989-1990 (Box JGS 8, Folder 4)
- Lajos, Balogh, 1991 (Box JGS 8, Folder 5)
- Lan, circa 1990 (Box JGS 8, Folder 6)
- Landgraf, Ken, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 7)
- Landgren, Don, 1989 (Box JGS 8, Folder 8)
- Lang, Roman, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 9)
- Langer, Matthias, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 8, Folder 10)
- Langer, Sergio, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 11)
- Langer, Sven, circa 1986 (Box JGS 8, Folder 12)
- Langhans, Pavel, 1990-1993 (Box JGS 8, Folder 13)
- Langridge, Roger, 1989 (Box JGS 8, Folder 14)
- Lanzo, O.G., 1992-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 15)
- LaPalme, Robert, 1984-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 78)
- Lapi (Pires), 1986-1990 (Box JGS 8, Folder 16)
- Larson, Gary, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 8, Folder 17)
- Lash, Batton, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 8, Folder 18)
- Lash, Glenn, 1985-1988 (Box JGS 8, Folder 19)
- Lasswell, Fred, 1989-1996 (Box JGS 8, Folder 20)
- LAT (Mohd Nor Khalid), 1991 (Box JGS 8, Folder 21)
- Latifi, G.A., undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 22)
- Lauck, Johnny, 1996 (Box JGS 8, Folder 23)
- Laucks, Rein, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 24)
- Laybourn, Mel, 1983 (Box JGS 8, Folder 25)
- Lazarus, Mell, 1990-1992 (Box JGS 8, Folder 26)
- Leach, Ken, 1990 (Box JGS 8, Folder 27)
- Leahy, Sean, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 28)
- Leatherbarrow, Tim, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 29)
- LeBars, Nikolaz, 1993 (Box JGS 8, Folder 30)
- LeBlanc, Andre, circa 1986 (Box JGS 8, Folder 31)
- LeDoux, Harold, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 32)
- Lee, Bill, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 8, Folder 33)
- Lee, Yong-Myong, 1989-1992 (Box JGS 8, Folder 34)
- Leedy, Jeff, 1984-1996 (Box JGS 8, Folder 35)
- Lefkowitz, S., 1988-1992 (Box JGS 8, Folder 36)